{"id": "3XDSWAMB246TTF2NW6ALKCP4V9GCQG##3K9FOBBF2KY4G6HVJTH58LGB9EQNLV##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1385180##q1_a1##3AXFSPQOYSCJA4IKSIGDVHYLGIGFJN", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Until we can get you an ice pack that 'll have to do . \" She held it in her hands like a treasure , sparkling . \" Thank you so much Fujimoto - san ! \" Before he could fight back another blush she had opened the can and was chugging it back . His jaw dropped and he was momentarily flabbergasted . The crowd murmured in concern and disapproval .\n\nQuestion: What may the female subject have drank based off reactions ?", "options": {"A": "She may have drank water .", "B": "She may have drank alcohol .", "C": "She may have drank some tap water .", "D": "She may have drank juice ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 20952, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3XQ4XW3ODBQS8DPYRHAK3ZVJ3V42SI##3ZSY5X72N0QX1PCKPSEE9MPF9SLORU##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_985759##q1_a1##3ZUE82NE0CFUQNM11EJM6RP70HDF8E", "type": "mcq", "stem": "He placed his hand on David 's head , running his hand throwing his hair in a very comforting manner . \" I ' m going to be right here , okay ? \" Michael told David . He felt the musician nod .\n\nQuestion: What may the musician be getting ready for ?", "options": {"A": "An interview .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "A tour .", "D": "A concert ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 3648, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3WUVMVA7ODHEES6GZOX75ABK2CRZAE##36U2A8VAG4EN8Z3R5VEFA113U4BYKX##A29RROPO0Z90XV##Blog_1183346##q1_a1##3JYPJ2TAYKMFWFLINVLXSDKYQ8BPF7", "type": "mcq", "stem": "First the bad news : Even though the movie 's called Booty Call , you wo n't be seeing Vivica A. Fox 's booty in the hook - up comedy . Now the good news : Viv 's shivs do make a pointed appearance . In the free pic of Vivica A.\n\nQuestion: Why does he want to see her booty ?", "options": {"A": "He does n't like Vivica .", "B": "He is attracted to Vivica .", "C": "He wanted to see a fox .", "D": "He is attracted to men ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 819, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3UV0D2KX1OXT7MZZPBT9PF92YZ4F42##3OVR4I9USSYTLVN2TTA5QY95YA64QE##A2WPPQC8S3ICVZ##Blog_836283##q1_a1##3ZRKL6Z1EAHIN7X5QWV953PLE7UGSP", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Ok , So i had went camping for almost two weeks , and it was a blast ! Me and my cousin had went swimming , and we had met these boys up at the beach . And one was so flipping HOT his name is Chad .\n\nQuestion: What may be true about me ?", "options": {"A": "I am afraid of the ocean .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "I have a boyfriend .", "D": "I like spending time outdoors ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 24299, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3YD0MU1NC2ZG0T13WVTOMSUDYZ47A3##36U2A8VAG2X8DA4KLY2FI3DUHUNKYD##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_772473##q1_a1##3A9LA2FRWSCPPVF8KE7EXDU5E1KHXN", "type": "mcq", "stem": "God answered my prayers ! I knew that we would be working on our anniversary but I sent out a prayer that please , please could He make it a special one for me ? I am such a sucker for celebrating events .\n\nQuestion: Why did the narrator pray to god to avoid work ?", "options": {"A": "The narrator loved work over celebrating personal events .", "B": "The narrator had no desire to celebrate their anniversary .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "The narrator truly loved their work and was passionate about it ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 9012, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3D06DR5225HZLW8Q01VD5AR3TOZAMH##30H4UDGLT3G9UKCMFNJCKPCM2QMMPP##A13H5EYMWJ9GU8##Blog_523693##q1_a1##3L1EFR8WWT3FA364M8D0EPWARI3F9P", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I got a laundry last night , and I dare say I am as excited as a woman who has just upgraded from a wringer to a brand true electric washing machine . Or from a washboard to a wringer . Or from a stone in the river to a washboard ... well you get the idea .\n\nQuestion: Why was the woman excited", "options": {"A": "She just repaired her washing machine", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "She just got a new washing machine", "D": "She just bought some new clothes"}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 8024, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "33P2GD6NRNQJ5VG1LVSP7JM3I9HHK8##39ZSFO5CA9UWLHEXTC5EE374AS0JUT##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_462526##q1_a1##3VADEH0UHEBO0KQ4TFLWZC3CE6CPSA", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I look over my shoulder and the man is sweating like two rats in a wool sock ; very Flashdance - esque . Finally he and his stench leave . I look over at the treadmill . It 's covered in sweat .\n\nQuestion: What might be a fact about the person in this situation ?", "options": {"A": "They are trying to lose weight by working out .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "They are working out at a gym .", "D": "They are trying to build muscle at the gym ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 7314, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "31MCUE39BKKZ91DJGJI85XT0SX43GQ##3H8DHMCCWA95FZ9TP2F15I3T4PIKDD##A1DBE2OL84TBKB##Blog_1273764##q1_a1##3WGZLY9VCJ0XS385A8OWIRMMO0E8D5", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Tocadisco is playing there next Friday and it 's only 5 bucks to get in so I 'll definitely be back there next week . I ' m really in love with this city . Walking around tonight was fun and I feel like I ' m getting more of a grip on where things are . I ' m amazed by how lenient the herb laws are here in San Fran .\n\nQuestion: Why Does he love San Francisco so much ?", "options": {"A": "It is a lot warmer than the old city", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "A lot of his hobbies are cheap or free", "D": "He is free to grow herbs"}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 4572, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3Z8UJEJOC1RZOGPIMBOY5EVLGWD938##3QXNC7EIPLA6U8OFTQCHS0T33LA092##A3218IMDX9KLPJ##Blog_794674##q1_a2##3Z8UJEJOC1RZOGPIMBOY5EVLHU739T", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Seeing as I was in bed at just past 6 AM or so and had to get up at 12 to get ready , it was quite understandable why I was n't entirely too proud with myself as I went to bed . Strangely , though , I managed to get up on time and even showered and all that jazz . I was n't entirely able to stomach any breakfast , though , so I ended up having a few Pepsis which was probably not the best idea in the world . As I headed off towards Tina 's , I found myself staggering a bit too much for my liking , so I ended up having to really pull myself together to appear somewhat normal and coherent as I arrived .\n\nQuestion: What may be a plausible reason I was staggering on the way to Tina â€™s ?", "options": {"A": "I only got a few hours of sleep .", "B": "I drank too much pepsi .", "C": "I could not stomach my breakfast .", "D": "I was walking as if I felt way too proud of myeslf ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 24132, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3P888QFVX3SF8F0J2D7CNEVDTFFQOH##32UTUBMZ7HUQGD5LAA22C1QAIMCVB7##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1407163##q1_a2##3G3AJKPCXN6Z7DGUU1LXE0GI43W4YC", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Serious diet pills are intended for people who are overweight to the point of being considered obese . Therefore , they are known as anti - obesity drugs ; and should not be used for quick , temporary weight loss . Diet medications and supplements will not simply \" melt \" away all your unwanted fat and permanently solve any weight problem you might have . Most weight loss trials show that diet pills offer ( at best ) short term support . You should use diet pills in combination with a simple plan for weight loss through regular exercise and an improved diet .\n\nQuestion: Why is the narrator so down on diet pills ?", "options": {"A": "They do n't believe they should be legal .", "B": "They do n't believe anything can make them lose weight .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "They do n't believe they do what they claim ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 3358, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3T6SSHJUZHO7PK04B81YMDWDG3DIIC##32N49TQG3JX0SSZ0OTE69OUDY2VAVA##AO33H4GL9KZX9##Blog_1305958##q1_a1##3P458N04Q3V04UBXLRG727CBI8R2X7", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I got a little scared , ngl . I ' m home alone and it kept thundering and lightening and pouring . And now I ' m laying on my couch with Lady Bug and Charlie . And Bogie is laying on the floor next to us :] I feel like I ' m going to throw up .\n\nQuestion: Why is everyone sitting nearby each other during the thunderstorm ?", "options": {"A": "Because being near each other makes us feel the thunderstorm is bigger .", "B": "Because being near each other makes us feel safer and more comfortable .", "C": "Because being near each other makes us feel more dangerous and daring .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 22174, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3D17ECOUOG9HZBMNIY95Q8D2J9R31A##3ND9UOO81NHU30Q9BU8S44T262EWL7##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_1266623##q1_a1##3U18MJKL1W08QIPVGEI4GIUZSZKNCZ", "type": "mcq", "stem": "So finally I have the time to make some more updates . School has started and I ' m on a bus for one hour going and one hour coming back . That s the price you pay to go to the best all girls school in the district .\n\nQuestion: Why do n't they have much spare time ?", "options": {"A": "School is taking up their time .", "B": "Family is taking up their time .", "C": "Extracurricular activities are taking up their time .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 24270, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3VCK0Q0PO5C921V8K0DKTJ4QQZ10NZ##3JNQLM5FT5KTWVTVDD7LOZP4WCGL2I##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1073242##q1_a2##3O2Y2UIUCS8ELOO2A3GPWWYYVE5KFU", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I had heard they were out of the meatball and I got anxious my order was n't going to be filled , so when I found out that mine was the last meatball sandwich , I was so excited I nearly peed . But it was n't that good . Neon pink , so I thought that meant it would be bursting with flavor , like Bubblicious or something , but no ! alas !\n\nQuestion: Why did the narrator have a great lunch ?", "options": {"A": "They got the first meatball sandwich .", "B": "They got a fine date to join them .", "C": "They got exactly what they ordered .", "D": "They got vegetarian meatballs ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 17870, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3PZDSVZ3J5FQ1PD9310M5MU37104NI##3ZR9AIQJUC7Q2DJWSY4QJUUECHS04O##A37IJGXG1VEBEK##Blog_463879##q1_a1##3IZVJEBJ6CYDRQUD9BGVP59Y6F3Z6Y", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Speed II 9/10 Monsoonz 10/10 Both kites produce colossal amounts of lift . Stand on the beach and pull down the bar ... up you go . The Monsoonz was my favourite here for sure ... pull in the bar and up I went ... ooohhh baby ! ! ... it was love at first flight ... I guess this why they go up wind so well .\n\nQuestion: What kind of product was I reviewing ?", "options": {"A": "A hang glider", "B": "A surfboard", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "A airplanr"}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 2848, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3421H3BM9CVA9UR7PWGLLLCADPH9JV##3R08VXYT7FAVOF17707ILZB1CE87W1##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_696570##q1_a1##3EFNPKWBMU2HSM15MF55C3USEVW037", "type": "mcq", "stem": "He could hear her breathing - slow , regulated . He felt that familiar pang from somewhere inside the darkness that he denied . That slow , relaxed - unknowing - breathing of prey being watched . He selfishly would miss these moments if she was turned .\n\nQuestion: What may be the reason for someone being so jealous of breathing ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "They have a respiratory illness .", "C": "They are n't human .", "D": "They are an animal ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 19349, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "388FBO7JZRR6ZWRTS8OTLBYA2LXYNX##3LKC68YZ3B1NEWUZ4PCK4N9NWS7OWK##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_1144267##q2_a1##3VLL1PIENS23GW0H972P65VPRQVZO7", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I think I need to go to the bridge tonight . I need to calm my heart and mind . I was told that it appears that no man will ever settle me . This statement is false because one man once did and did it successfully for over 6 years .\n\nQuestion: What may be a fact about this person ?", "options": {"A": "No one wants to settle down with them .", "B": "They will be single for a long time .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "They had a failed long - term relationship ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 13825, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3909MD9T21VBZOWSEH5MY1LTBOZEF8##3DHE4R9OCZQS5SE1MJM535858AIG2I##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_988620##q1_a1##3B9XR6P1WG9TXN64NGUHCR712BPJBV", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Cos of her really frizzy hair and low voice ... It was so freaking cold so I ' m really impressed by these actors ' professionalism , they were prancing about ( at least Desdemona was ) in thin clothing and they still acted so well . I was like shivering in my seat throughout , especially during the first half when I did n't have my jacket . Ran up to my room during the 15 min interval for my jacket and spoke to Cassio and Othello with Ernest and Sid . But I was still damn cold and kept on fidgeting during the play .\n\nQuestion: What may be the reason for them not bringing the jacket with them in the first place ?", "options": {"A": "They did n't think they would need it .", "B": "They are usually always hot .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "They did n't think they would be staying for the whole show ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 1041, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "36818Z1KV5RDTZZNEH2Y1965N5IA3U##3OONKJ5DKFYALIVVTVSO97KBRAQOBX##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_299306##q1_a1##38RHULDV90TPQFK90P5DN45LYGCIWR", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Will they be quick to criticize when promised jobs do not materialize , the national debt does not decline , and jobs continue to go overseas ? Will they , whose candidate is elected President think all of their problems will vanish , and never to reappear ? Nothing is further from the truth . History shows that power remains in the hands of a chosen few , no matter who is President .\n\nQuestion: What is the narrator so focused on and ranting about ?", "options": {"A": "They are ranting about power supply .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "They are ranting about politics .", "D": "They are ranting about the President of Canada ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 976, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "35O6H0UNLUUR87PVM6349578R0DJ57##3DIP6YHAPF757TKZW55IDT0WHT18E0##A1GV0UZU0T2ORS##Blog_280385##q2_a2##3P458N04Q3V04UBXLRG727CCJ3FX2J", "type": "mcq", "stem": "At this point i really need to stress how much of a religious experience i had with the Osama Tezuka exhibition that was going on on the first floor of of the place . For those of you not too familiar with anime or manga culture , Tezuka was the main originator of ALL the genres of anime that are being pooped out today . And compared to the crazy epic manga he produced in the 1960s and 70s , today 's manga is all pretty much recycled crap .\n\nQuestion: What can we deduce about the narrator in this passage ?", "options": {"A": "They do n't like Osama Tezuka .", "B": "They are a manga fan .", "C": "They are religious .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 3070, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3BDORL6HKMRT5GHN9LZLP2Z9TMJRCH##3GGAI1SQEYD5VK2PUF96SN1OEZWMCG##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_1434547##q1_a1##3AA88CN98RHKLF5XFT8DLH5E1S1KY3", "type": "mcq", "stem": "We ' ve barely finished painting the rooms . I ' ve hired someone to change the floor in the basement from ( ugh ) carpet to wood ( laminate ) . I ca n't afford real hardwood now , and the quality of today 's laminates are good enough .\n\nQuestion: What may be the reason for someone hiring someone to install the flooring ?", "options": {"A": "They do n't want the flooring installed .", "B": "They are helping someone out by paying them to do it .", "C": "They do n't know how to do it .", "D": "They do n't like flooring ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 7164, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3XQ4XW3ODBQS8DPYRHAK3ZVJ3TGS2G##3TS1AR6UQTTTDTFCHBXIHBP1G3HF7T##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1360236##q1_a1##3P7RGTLO6GRJPX7UZNUXIVN7Y1PAKA", "type": "mcq", "stem": "The music was amazing and the food was possibly the best I ' ve ever had . Half the Island was a wildlife preserve so there were beautiful birds everywhere . I ca n't even give a good description of what it all looked and smelled like , I would not do it justice .\n\nQuestion: Why was there so much wildlife around ?", "options": {"A": "It was at a zoo .", "B": "It was protected lands .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "It was at a zoo - like amusement park ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 7623, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3ZQX1VYFTFJOW0ZU0H2CTLYLQHDO8E##3PH3VY7DJOCE8P7DQVZ1CJ40HZ1ZWG##AABCSDU3TZLNG##Blog_668164##q2_a1##35U0MRQMULLM7CV78ADMLZIT36DOV2", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I had the scariest experience ever last night , and I was in a car this time!My brother - in - Law and I were coming home from his birthday dinner and as he was turning left onto a street , my husband said \" bike \" , which did n't register to anyone else at firat until he yelled \" BIKE ! ! \" and we saw a woman whiz past in my BIL 's headlights , a mere couple of feet from his bumper . He slammed on the breaks and we were all like \" HOLY SHIIIIIT ! ! ! \"\n\nQuestion: How did we feel after the brother - in - law stopped ?", "options": {"A": "We were full from eating .", "B": "We were stunned and shocked .", "C": "We wanted to ride bikes .", "D": "We were slammed and broken ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 16559, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3KTZHH2ONIDL28FB33BZ9JL83008MC##3VE8AYVF8NVIIILO7JDO3DXNHTJF8T##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_453107##q1_a2##3FO95NVK5CYUI87CM9DLC9FJMX4SRF", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Mentally ill mothers who were unable to understand how to meet their children 's needs raised many of my Schizophrenic and depressed clients . Over our years together , when a depressive fog floated from the wings , Jim tried his best to understand my experience . One of the ways he helped was by carrying on as usual .\n\nQuestion: What may the narrator think if he has a new mentally disturbed patient ?", "options": {"A": "That they had a bad stretch in life lately .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "That they had a ill parent growing up .", "D": "That they are in need of medicine ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 19726, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "336OE47KI4YUCL49ZW4W2TVF6MRWVT##3Z4AIRP3C9SW2TRVSPMVM8YVJUP1X3##A2CMYWI1J292YJ##Blog_13505##q1_a2##3VGET1QSZ2DS1V3DHY1GWFFDLH87WT", "type": "mcq", "stem": "We called every kennel in the metropolitan area to find that they were a ) booked solid or b ) charged quadruple our regular rate . No way were we taking our carsick - prone pooch with us . Thank goodness for our fabulous friends T. & T. who agreed to dog sit . We owe them a lifetime supply of adult beverages . Then , our neighbor stole our car .\n\nQuestion: Why are they charging much more than before ?", "options": {"A": "They are trying to recoup the renovation cost .", "B": "They are featured in a pet magazine .", "C": "Supply is much smaller than demand now .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 869, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3QREJ3J433VLRRZRCG7NZBFAZ4IKL2##308XBLVESJ2YN6O41QXSB417XNOBRX##A32W24TWSWXW##Blog_820789##q1_a1##36D1BWBEHPFPAICT7KEYRQWDBFLM27", "type": "mcq", "stem": "After that discussion we said a few thanks for the Light and she asked what I 'd learned about holy power . As a student of axe and spell , I told her of what I knew , which was n't much beyond simple spells and prayers , but I think she was pleased , and we ate well that night . Next morning , Pa was really thinking we needed to explore . There was some place he was trying to find , some memory from the wars that happened there . Unfortunately the Murlocs had taken over but we did n't know that then . It was a little shack in the middle of the swampy northern Wetlands , there was no one around when we came upon it .\n\nQuestion: What may have been the reason we were in danger when we went to the shack ?", "options": {"A": "The area had been taken over by an enemy and we were trespassing on their turf .", "B": "We had no food at the time and were weak because we had n't eaten for several days .", "C": "I had learned too much about the holy power and that was detrimental when dealing with Murlocs .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 18390, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3HJ1EVZS2OHQYRMXWUCK4177UYT3RK##3IXQG4FA2UWSJ6SI79X6KJ1DPCIB9U##A37IJGXG1VEBEK##Blog_430615##q1_a1##3WYZV0QBFLRUS7BT4K9I30FFCGIBX0", "type": "mcq", "stem": "So yesterday I called up their support center to try to get the problem fixed . Microsoft was willing to work on the case despite the fact that I bought the console used from GameStop . After futzing around for a while with cables and trying to get it working , they suggested that I get a new A / V cable . So I went out and bought myself a new A / V cable .\n\nQuestion: What may i be trying to get fixed ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "My playstation", "C": "My laptop", "D": "My x box"}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 6515, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3E24UO25QZOMYXHZN4TEH9EMT5V6OA##36AHBNMV1SA0Z4YATHGSEQI41ESDYL##A3H0TLQC53H5MB##Blog_847948##q2_a1##3PN6H8C9R64BBR1K768AEISHEJKDAA", "type": "mcq", "stem": "No flying brooms . Bugger ! But the bludgers were contorted teddy - bears , and the snitch was a Nemo squeaky rubber toy , and for all that I thought I 'd only gone to be a spectator , I ended up as one of the volunteers who threw the snitch * and * thoroughly enjoyed myself , despite having problems seeing the snitch on occasions . The number of players increased , play hotted up and became fiercely competitive , but also wildly fun .\n\nQuestion: What fictional character might the OP be ?", "options": {"A": "Harry Potter", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "Beatrice Prior", "D": "Evan Walker"}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 23462, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3R5LWXWHR06BPZKX08PWCDI4ZWBGXH##33M4IA01QHZ509R56MPA01SZGLCXRI##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_277735##q1_a1##3WRAAIUSBLDP9X61Y69M8PV9U7YAXN", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Today I asked Josh if we had a socket wrench . He showed me how to actually use one , and together we detached the whole fan mechanism , reattached the screw , put the whole thing back together , and voila ! The fan works like new . Our apartment is cooler , and the peasants rejoiced .\n\nQuestion: What may be a fact about the person speaking ?", "options": {"A": "They had to purchase a new fan .", "B": "They had to get a new fan for their apartment .", "C": "They had fixed their broken fan .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 21295, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3UOMW19E6FK40TJPCEMIM1UD0S6C5B##3B2X28YI3ZUKWCPRTZ6US7YK34FB6Z##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_727903##q2_a1##33QQ60S6AUW1RGEO1Z16ZCKSR0GU0T", "type": "mcq", "stem": "It was basically the same every day . Wake up , put on clothes , eat breakfast , weed and then shower . In the middle of the day I would do desk work or we would lay around reading .\n\nQuestion: What may be the reason for their routine ?", "options": {"A": "They want to minimize socializing .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "They are used to it .", "D": "They want to stay inside ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 22981, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3IVEC1GSLRDSKPOCLJ1S6FUREHB1J3##39DD6S19JSQKRPLM5V5VQDX0COSEZZ##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_645909##q2_a1##3IKDQS3DQGEGCHE4JY5CBAYI6X6CII", "type": "mcq", "stem": "It 's a long way to be sustainable country in China . but these nice persons action will change China for sustainable country all over the world . I will walk through China and all over the world not only for China for our earth .\n\nQuestion: How might this person be described ?", "options": {"A": "They are an active person .", "B": "They are an athletic person .", "C": "They are an activist for the environment .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 17856, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3NSM4HLQNT8XNGC61OBG4HEL1OPQQ9##3C44YUNSI44LLF5GMRW9TXD159LDPG##A35BKXOE6C5ITG##Blog_1248339##q2_a1##32K26U12DP2V3F4II1Z6A56UZ53DVH", "type": "mcq", "stem": "We knew there was a tyre shop in Killarney so we rode the spare till we got there . On the way we stopped at my favorite place of the whole trip . It was \" Molly 's Tea Room . \"\n\nQuestion: what is molly 's tea room most likely ?", "options": {"A": "a place to order tea", "B": "a place that gives films about tea", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "a place that does not sell tea"}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 13746, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3538U0YQ1FSTV1HO5ZCQNCTORMA3F5##3EF8EXOTT2TGCKNZROVU31271ORJ16##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_339042##q1_a1##3XABXM4AJ3JRHCCAFUUGIQTL7GAQ81", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I have a friend who maintains that I have extra - ordinary curiosity and she dislikes the way I stop and gaze at something that has caught my fancy . I must admit sometimes I get carried away especially with planes and I once landed into a ditch because an aircraft that was passing quite low near my university in London , looked good to my eyes ! I like jets and I ' m already dreaming of travelling in the colossal Airbus A380 ! !\n\nQuestion: Why is the friend getting annoyed with the narrator ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "The narrator keeps staring at things .", "C": "The narrator is difficult to work with at university .", "D": "The narrator is dropping out of university ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 7223, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "33K3E8REWWTWWKEFHAD8K016AI88XC##3LO69W1SU4BJBP12CSSAQ3J52STLGZ##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_939412##q1_a1##3D5G8J4N5A2NQF18KTNLNB089N1VT8", "type": "mcq", "stem": "So this morning I thought I was being proactive and getting dinner in the crock pot to cook all day . The idea of smelling a brisket with potatoes and carrots and onions cooking all say sounded heavenly . I got everything all chopped up and into the crock pot . I threw in some chopped up garlic and put the lid on .\n\nQuestion: What is the narrator desiring next once her prep is done ?", "options": {"A": "The narrator will want to go on a fast .", "B": "The narrator will want to make food .", "C": "The narrator will want to eat .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 14719, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3NSCTNUR211G7EMRS0QRG64PZA8A5Z##3K3R2QNK8EIMAU0VRXQ1H7HAGASU9A##A1VYRD3HO2WDUN##Blog_677613##q1_a1##3TUOHPJXYJBMGA94ZB5EQES0MJKXWQ", "type": "mcq", "stem": "So we hugged and I left Dan to the care of the airline - this time , however , not stuck in a wheelchair , and not shivering with a fever . So , much better than last time!I rode the trains back to Wada , uneventfully , except to say that I had to stand for an hour and a half or so , at the start of it all , as there were no seats left in the trains . I got back to Wada at 7 pm , and I took a taxi ( GASP , YES ) from Wada station to the old people 's home near my house . Why ?\n\nQuestion: What may be a valid fact about the train ?", "options": {"A": "Dan and I rode on it .", "B": "It was packed with riders .", "C": "It stopped right by my house .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 19309, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3FI30CQHVMXH9SRX3X0S3N2VFGJ6B9##3MYYFCXHJ6M286TOQX5TWK53QC74G5##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_823731##q1_a1##3Y7LTZE0YV0YT1KE5TEY5BNE9EEUZE", "type": "mcq", "stem": "We rigged it up so that it works again , but it 's no longer a textbook SPL system . We 're going to keep up the meds for another week , but reduce her Banamine from 500 # twice a day to 500 # once a day . Rosie did not act like a lady for Megan today .\n\nQuestion: What may be the reason why they needed to adjust the medicine ?", "options": {"A": "They could n't afford it anymore .", "B": "They wanted to see if she did n't need it anymore .", "C": "They want to try a natural approach .", "D": "It was no longer working ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 9115, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3TL87MO8CMNAB57DB5GQJYN5R1ELF0##3ITXP059PXHG64MT47AEZ2PGPM9JSP##A2KYOM2ZGYDJGT##Blog_1032625##q1_a1##3DZKABX2ZKJLYNY4I54VQZOCEUACVD", "type": "mcq", "stem": "We did our first track and were stopped by the manager - turn down or get off . It almost came to blows when , standing in the tin shed and unable to hear above the amp hum , he thought we were giving him lip . We turned down and trundled through the first few songs with decided lacklustre . After a bit of tweaking we got to a decent level and kicked out the last three tracks with vim and vigour ( and some good ol' head banging).Mark from Psych Carni had gone all out with lights , smoke , P.A.\n\nQuestion: What 's the possible reason they were stopped by the manager ?", "options": {"A": "They were standing in a tin shed .", "B": "The music was too loud .", "C": "They finished the first track .", "D": "They wanted to come to blows ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 212, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "30OITAWPBSHEIOWH1WD098WV0SIH9T##3MYYFCXHJ6M286TOQX5TWK53QYNG45##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1261836##q1_a2##3UOMW19E6FK40TJPCEMIM1UD1EP5CW", "type": "mcq", "stem": "As I mentioned before , we were fortunate enough to be in Reykjavik when the silver medal handball team came home . It was really nice to be part of the festivities and celebration . It felt as though a large majority of the Icelandic people were there , considering so many people showed up . While we were walking through town we saw their plane fly into the city airport escorted by two helicopters and we knew it would be a large event .\n\nQuestion: Why was so many people at the airport ?", "options": {"A": "To cheer the visiting Icelandic team .", "B": "To cheer the home team .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "To cheer the visiting team from Reykjavic ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 24864, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "36MUZ9VAE8GE14IWNBAWA1I8ZX5EDR##3WR9XG3T66QJFDINXU1ZQ7SARTJ744##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_802230##q1_a1##3M47JKRKCZFY7UTQ0LGICLCU7IE686", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Of course , 1812 completely ignored Mija , and I was able to distract her from her fearsome guarding behavior with a chance to play tug - of - war with the pheasant stuffie . Tired of the stuffie , we then moved on to my favorite toy . Early in the evening , I carried the pheasant stuffie outside to see if I could get anyone to play with me . Peaches looked like she might want to play , but Mija was a bit unsure about getting in a game that involved the alpha dog .\n\nQuestion: What kind of pets does the speaker have ?", "options": {"A": "Cats .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "Birds .", "D": "Dogs ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 5231, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3NQUW096N8MG4KF7SHSY10P2HL29LR##30LB5CDZNFPL0Z6SXO6G5OVWM1VZ07##A1GV0UZU0T2ORS##Blog_1169926##q2_a1##351S7I5UGBAVYWV1Q6ZQ3M7VJ0RNJC", "type": "mcq", "stem": "No ! Just because I do n't go around saying how hot my boss is , and I instead take to insulting her when I damn well please , does n't mean I ' m obsessed with her ! \" \" Uhm ... I think you are , \" Antoine said tentatively . I glared at him .\n\nQuestion: Why did I shoot Antoine the look that I did ?", "options": {"A": "It 's made me sarcastic .", "B": "It 's made me happy .", "C": "It 's made me angry .", "D": "It makes me want to laugh ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 22876, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "324N5FAHSZP3HLASAILTEI1KJ3IKVX##3TMFV4NEPBTZOT6QH5ZOZZ7WMHSW8S##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1144472##q1_a1##3TZ0XG8CBWYLPDVOYSJUWV3WXKX98X", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I met with my advisor / prof yesterday about my upcoming paper . In the process of emails and the meeting , he offered me a super sweet deal on a faculty apartment near the school . I took it and had to drag my stuff there this morning .\n\nQuestion: What type of school is the narrator in ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "They are at university .", "C": "They are at a prep school .", "D": "They are at an advisory school ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 13848, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "39RRBHZ0AWFY6G9EAJO31XPXLJGVZR##3PXX5PX6L0DLJE1UJCN68C06X3PBA3##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_484625##q1_a1##3LAZVA75NK5DALX5K0TBJULI68KO2U", "type": "mcq", "stem": "She laughed and said that she guessed she had more to live for than she had realized . At the end of the visit , she told me that I had been a great help and had really changed her attitude . Always makes me feel good .\n\nQuestion: What may be a fact about the person speaking ?", "options": {"A": "They worried about their friend .", "B": "They are a therapist .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "They are the girl 's parent ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 11149, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3W31J70BAUA7IC4SJ1QOOQDVYS4KCS##3DPNQGW4LOU0BD4IEKW7KTSEWFG46D##ALI92G1065WRG##Blog_685342##q2_a1##307FVKVSYTTGSTKT7SVX1NWL07Y74V", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Unlike outside and backstage , it was cool in the bus . He mentally thanked their bus driver for switching on the airco this morning as he made his way to the living room area . He flopped down on the large , brown sofa and closed his eyes , sighing again .\n\nQuestion: What is probably true about the people on the bus ?", "options": {"A": "They are moving a brown sofa .", "B": "They collectively play music .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "They are training to be bus drivers ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 9105, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3RBI0I35XGHEPHXQUNGE4VOCQ8VY3Q##3GA6AFUKOR3VQ65VAPIS7FPYTN13HJ##A1GV0UZU0T2ORS##Blog_1453841##q2_a1##3D3B8GE89456V5U5K9L5IHYNNAGP9F", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Today we drove a long long time . We had to take Tia Pica to the airport to fly in her plane home . I was sad she had to leave . I told mommy I missed her , after she had gone . I wish I could go visit daddy and Tia Pica .\n\nQuestion: Of these choices , where is the relative likely flying home to ?", "options": {"A": "Berlin", "B": "Mexico", "C": "Canada", "D": "Japan"}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 5094, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3ROUCZ907FSCN3N3N0F8Y90DE05OON##3E13VNJ1NOTKH93T96AUR0N7MGOI1R##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1225044##q1_a1##3EGKVCRQFY6JSC139GVKMEMOENUBYQ", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Last night i had this dream where i was walking into my kitchen . It was dark out so i was about to turn the light on when i saw a silhouette of a person coming towards me . I was n't scared just curious .\n\nQuestion: What is the narrator reading into their recent dream ?", "options": {"A": "They are worried about the stranger .", "B": "They are worried about the fire .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "They are worried about the natural disaster ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 7055, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3HJ1EVZS2OHQYRMXWUCK4177UALR3O##3MYYFCXHJ45NDHUH60TT4MHULGKG4C##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1139780##q1_a1##3P888QFVX58U24ZQMBJCFCJLMLEQO4", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I know all you mom 's are thinking I ca n't believe Randi lets him do that ! Well you can spend your whole life being careful and then look back on your whole life and realize you never lived or you can take some chances , have a lot of fun , and suffer a few scrapes along the way . Well a few days ago we had our first accident and our first scrapes along the way .\n\nQuestion: Why is the narrator not too worried about the accident ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "They feel Randi was n't hurt in it .", "C": "They feel one has to take risks some time .", "D": "They feel there was no major damage ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 25018, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3BFF0DJK8XA7YNK4QYIGCOG1AINTSF##3FTYUGLFSVJ2XGOQIFBV3TKB8HZD5Y##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_1396999##q1_a1##3BO3NEOQM2VSJ2H6ZK9L5F8U6WPAIM", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Tonight marked the end of a long week , and Paul offered to take the kids home from my folks ' and put them to bed . We had two cars as he had , yet again , devoted a big chunk of his weekend to getting his parents ' house ready for sale -- a never - ending and thankless job if there ever was one . So I took him up on the offer and played hooky for a while . First , I drove down to the house Paul has been cleaning , emptying , repairing , painting , and re - wiring since June .\n\nQuestion: Why were they making adjustments to the house ?", "options": {"A": "The house was starting to fall apart .", "B": "They were preparing to sell it .", "C": "They were having issues with the house that needed fixing .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 11029, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3KG2UQJ0ML2CKJZELWJZ0NJGWD2QNM##3R0T90IZ1VR53A63JCBBFIHRJJVCGM##A3P46WP16JCU2V##Blog_1570385##q2_a1##3TZDZ3Y0JUK3EDB3Z7AFHLGOJGI918", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I do n't want to move out until I have at least 2,000 $ saved up in my account . and I owe my dad 150.00 $ from the car accident I got in a couple months ago , so I ' m going to try and pay him back . I want to get my new tattoo ! ! ! And I do n't want to get it until I pay him back the money I owe him .\n\nQuestion: What may have been the cause to borrow money from their dad ?", "options": {"A": "I spent my money on a new tatoo .", "B": "I was saving for a new car .", "C": "I was short on money when I had my car accident .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 3349, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "31KPKEKW4AB71S6BHA8B2O4W9ANB0L##3SLE99ER0OB7PXAVB7R5X7365RKZB0##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_480364##q1_a1##3GS542CVJX122VCM0UCRKBT5VQF592", "type": "mcq", "stem": "The paint on the main body is original and still look nice . Very miminal amount of dings and scratches . There 're a couple of bumps in the rear in the fiberglass , left rear lower and right rear corner .\n\nQuestion: How would one describe the condition of the car ?", "options": {"A": "The car is in terrible condition .", "B": "The car is in pristine condition .", "C": "The car is in mint condition .", "D": "The car is in good condition ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 3039, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3BFNCI9LYKOGG82INGEEZKG7S3137K##3TESA3PJ32839HF9N7RK3LIRYPYMMP##AO33H4GL9KZX9##Blog_1503487##q1_a1##3087LXLJ6MEXE9IRMCU7LEVHOIG0FD", "type": "mcq", "stem": "In addition to the claims that his rights have been violated , Griffin alleges that Mayor Thomas ' decision to extend the disaster declaration was done without a vote by the city council in violation of Texas law . Court assignment is pending . Case No .\n\nQuestion: Who has the authority to extend the disaster declaration ?", "options": {"A": "The mayor has the authority .", "B": "The city council has the authority .", "C": "The court has the authority .", "D": "Texas has the authority ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 12449, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "32W3UF2EZOJ7ALGIEBR8PB0R858C4A##39LNWE0K4VU0Q6URBUKE22S4YMKIU8##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1373461##q1_a1##306996CF6YYM26Q0XROB8RBE79X1B8", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Originally published at keat n candice . Please leave any comments there . With our new addition to the family , my dad got us more lanterns this year to create the Mid - Autumn Festival atmostphere . Baby Matt does n't know how to play with his lantern much this year , but come same time next year , we 'll most probably be keeping him away from those traditional candle - lit lanterns !\n\nQuestion: Why does the narrator have extra lanterns ?", "options": {"A": "Matt wanted them .", "B": "Their family needed them for lighting the home .", "C": "Their family grew .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 3169, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3XAOZ9UYRZPUCNTIWB91BII50QDQ1A##3D8YOU6S9FIKXMZQ9TBP5Z2ZOL6U6M##A3H0TLQC53H5MB##Blog_741839##q2_a1##3ODOP6T3AUY96SNN1GE25WFDPGI24U", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I think our team did a really good job in planning the event . Ok , so as for the actual event we came across a lot of PROBLEMS . The good thing was that fifteen minutes before our event started we had reached our limit so I was really excited about that . All the singers showed up so I was glad that nobody baled out on us .\n\nQuestion: What best describe 's the OP 's occupation ?", "options": {"A": "Music agent", "B": "Event coordinator", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "Talent vendor"}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 11763, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3RTFSSG7TAKRGGSFLS2QFKXDFMMLWS##369J354OFGPGNTX29LY8TIPHO6YG6V##A39SK1E6IMQBD5##Blog_1561700##q1_a1##3UOMW19E6FK40TJPCEMIM1UE2VIC5X", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Features customer benefits , energy saving tips , contact account home getting started products feature list pricing feng shui ; finance ; fishing ; fitness ; flirting ; games ; garage sale . Company the corcoran group , offers tips on house at percent less than the last sale in your neighborhood pricing is same steps you might take to announce a garage or yard sale . That lists privately owned cottages for rent and sale in see more information regarding tickets and pricing teenagers in the guest cabin over the garage . Have two great months of riding left on the front range and now is a great time to snag a great deal on a demo bike please see the master sale list for models and pricing .\n\nQuestion: What may be a plausible fact about what I wrote ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "I wrote a magazine .", "C": "I wrote an advertisement .", "D": "I wrote a book ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 11270, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "35O6H0UNLSECEIQO28R4H7J0XG45J3##3Z7VU45IPZF6CZS39AYGRVQXEJFZ16##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1270395##q1_a1##3EN4YVUOUCQLG1AY8EAZ9QAKRTNXJ7", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I do n't want you getting in trouble for being out past curfew . One more shot , and then I 'll walk you back to the common room . \" They assumed their positions .\n\nQuestion: Why is the narrator expressing so many nerves here ?", "options": {"A": "The narrator is not worried .", "B": "The narrator is confident .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "The narrator wants to avoid curfew trouble ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 19782, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3D7VY91L67BJYVCPQD79SJZH4NWMBA##32SVAV9L3IOGGJXH4J80QT2UDLDA30##A3218IMDX9KLPJ##Blog_408692##q2_a1##3PIOQ99R7004CC6V2534AOG5ZW7NUJ", "type": "mcq", "stem": "The 1 hour does NOT include thinking in the shower , procrastinating , setting up the video camera , editing the video , uploading to Core77 , or anything not related to creating the sick - assest rendering you can come up with . Use this Core77 4 minute sketch session as guidance for how to set - up your camera . If you 're a digital hack , a screen capture will do nicely .\n\nQuestion: What may happen if you are considered to be a digital hack ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "You will know how to utilize Core77 .", "C": "You can complete the whole process faster than the 1 hour suggestion .", "D": "You will be able to edit the video ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 8667, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3LB1BGHFL4AJOYVK92M5M8SAK78YT7##3BWI6RSP7JO17FFGM0DCZT4169T7EA##A1GV0UZU0T2ORS##Blog_1438535##q1_a2##3RKHNXPHGYA346LS5SBOIWZ26LKUKA", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I start the process 2 hours before I had to leave . I went upstairs with 30 minutes left , and it was only 5 % done ? I figure I have to be doing something wrong ... or the long way .\n\nQuestion: How much more of \" the process \" will the narrator have to do ?", "options": {"A": "only 5 % of it .", "B": "the majority of it .", "C": "a small part of it .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 1423, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3DQYSJDTYL9D5LO6UDZ8CAXSMIJXE8##3R0T90IZ1TAQ8L7WZFZBNKTID2GCGI##A22EDUBB602EJD##Blog_822076##q1_a1##3X878VYTIGWQQ9HIR9RGSRTCPU0F7E", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Today found me working on writing of the non - fiction variety . I finally got around ( forced ) myself to write up some of the recipes I ' ve had sitting here waiting to be added to my cooking blog . Doing this also forced me to figure out what the heck was going on with the coding as well - as it was looking something awful and it needed to be fixed . After wrestling with it for two hours I figured out the culprit was a particular post that had coding in it .\n\nQuestion: What is the hobby of this person that has a problem with computer coding ?", "options": {"A": "This person likes to engage in wrestling and other self defense things .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "This person likes to write recipes for his personal cooking blog .", "D": "This person enjoys reading non - fiction books and how to fix things ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 23911, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3XAOZ9UYRZPUCNTIWB91BII5045Q1U##3VELCLL3GLH07I138Y49O3AF8GCF1Z##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_463040##q1_a2##31SIZS5W5BTXZHR6E30G97OQX8YRQE", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I asked him the same question : he loves me for my heart . I believe he truly loves and cares about me , that I will always be in his heart ; but I also believe that he believes this is n't forever . I know he wants me to have children one day and have a big family , but he knows it 's not with him .\n\nQuestion: What is the future of this relationship ?", "options": {"A": "They will have a big family .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "They will have kids .", "D": "They will break up ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 15054, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3YOAVL4CA2VZC3QZQNNGS7PKAZT4Z0##38F71OA9GWBCYWMZLHZ70TMRCJ5MFN##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_994951##q1_a1##3NQUW096N8MG4KF7SHSY10P2HMML9P", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Lays had worked tirelessly on exploring the true depths of the machine Sector Seven kept hidden and he had made astounding discoveries . While no one knew what a nanite was back then , Lays had filled several note books with details of what he perceived as tiny machines that rebuilt the section of the skin he had removed from Ice Man . While frozen , the nanites were dormant . When they were exposed to any kind of energy , be it solar , atomic , or otherwise , they would revive and try to repair the damage done . Lays had died in 1988 , still a scientist for Sector Seven even as he had already reached the amazing age of ninety - five .\n\nQuestion: Why is Sector Seven so secretive ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "It has convicts working in it .", "C": "It has criminals working in it .", "D": "It has an Ice - like temperature ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 17571, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3EPG8DX9LM4NUISTHJ8O61TK01M5P0##3J88R45B2JDZJLAXDRXLN4GTM9OXPU##A2WPPQC8S3ICVZ##Blog_151071##q2_a1##3EGKVCRQFY6JSC139GVKMEMPFFYYB4", "type": "mcq", "stem": "During the return journey we took a different route . The sites were really awsome . When we reached Mysore , we struggled really hard to find the road to bangalore . There was a junction which showed us to go to right , to Bangalore . But when I turned back , after the car took right there was a board which showed direction to bangalore in the opposite direction .\n\nQuestion: What may be true about the signs ?", "options": {"A": "Both led to Mysore .", "B": "One led to Mysore .", "C": "Both were correct .", "D": "One was incorrect ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 4090, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3KTZHH2ONIDL28FB33BZ9JL84VN8MQ##32EYX73OY17DJ5XA1HENGUTVJ0JRUZ##AB1VYJNM0H69F##Blog_1383250##q2_a1##3PR3LXCWSHDB4EWW60VMCUKPOHX9X8", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I was supposed to be packing today , but Eileen came in and messed all my things up . Honestly . She ought to know better . She 's nine , after all .\n\nQuestion: What is the narrator supposed to be doing ?", "options": {"A": "They are supposed to be packing for Eileen .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "They are supposed to be helping Eileen with packing .", "D": "They are supposed to be putting certain items into bags ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 12403, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3ZQX1VYFTD392B0NGJQC1NADZ1L8O0##369J354OFE81S4YVPOM81K18FYZ6GC##A3H0TLQC53H5MB##Blog_1545687##q1_a1##3IWA71V4TKUOMVUY8TSASKTNYJ46XF", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I guess that really is n't the post offices fault though , as much as I would love to blame them for something else . Anyway , like I said , there was bad news . This was being provided by the people at Federal Student Aid .\n\nQuestion: What might have been lost in the mail ?", "options": {"A": "SAT scores", "B": "FASFA application", "C": "Immigration documents", "D": "APTS application"}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 2582, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3YLTXLH3DF4KGMDHYNXX3082CQ3PHB##320DUZ38G8KDGZD297GXAO6D2FPJGO##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_516594##q2_a1##3YD0MU1NC4FVUI0AGT5OEQILSBMA7P", "type": "mcq", "stem": "So having a great time at the house just hanging with my mom . Just listening to some music , talking about life , sharing scripture and really just enjoying each other 's company . You know I do n't think I 'd have been doing this three months ago on a friday night .\n\nQuestion: What may be the reason for them being with their mother ?", "options": {"A": "Their mother needed someone there for them .", "B": "They missed hanging out with their mother .", "C": "They were feeling upset and needed comfort .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 18089, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3UOMW19E6D4P64KISGAIU3658YXC53##3VP0C6EFSHU1KEUH0RK3EPL5CW26M0##AUTYWXILTACCR##Blog_1193878##q1_a1##3VW0145YL0QPGEA1E5KQQ7IUDNBJMP", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I was half way to the store when I realized I forgot my bags . Darn . Oh , well , Molly made good use of the Target bag . I think she slept on it for a couple of hours . And look at that !\n\nQuestion: What could have led to Molly going to sleep on the target bag ?", "options": {"A": "Molly is a dog , and will sleep anywhere , provided it 's soft and reasonably comfortable", "B": "Molly had n't slept in two days due to finals , and was so exhausted she could sleep anywhere", "C": "Molly had accidentally taken more valium than she was supposed to , and as a result blacked out", "D": "Molly was very drunk and did n't care where she passed out , as long as she was n't standing up"}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 9606, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3MDKGGG61QL2BPM7JLFDBJK9S8T6T3##3QL2OFSM97GWIDOIMJC6D42FCERCND##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_811052##q1_a2##356TQKY9XHBHBU7VJVLAIZCQ2I087N", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I ' m a summer baby . My eldest is a summer baby . Summer babies do n't get to celebrate birthdays with cupcakes during school time . Summer babies do get their presents distributed better around the year .\n\nQuestion: Why does the narrator have a bit of resentment about school ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "They got treated poorly in school .", "C": "They did n't get to have a birthday party in school .", "D": "They did n't get treated well in school ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 20599, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3IVKZBIBJ07HTET9Q41RY5DDZHMHS9##3S4AW7T80CG3Z98IHRQ9HEM2HYJ4LL##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_278752##q1_a2##3XAOZ9UYR1596CSPG9L13G6DTA51QT", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Our assignment was to dial up the electric stimulation and measure how high the current needed to go at a given frequency in order to establish sensory threshold ( when you first begin to feel a tingle ) and motor threshold ( when muscles first begin to twitch ) . We started with 2 Hz which is two pulses per second . Then we delivered 25 Hz or 25 pulses per second . Finally , we went up to 100 Hz or 100 pulses of electrical stimulation per second .\n\nQuestion: What might be a fact about what they are testing ?", "options": {"A": "They are testing out current frequencies on the human body .", "B": "They are testing out how to electrocute someone .", "C": "They are testing out electric currents on muscles .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 20267, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "31ANT7FQN80GNCVYE8OJ5U3LLXEH57##3A9AA95ATXKBMDRGNO2Q3N10M51P5X##A1VR49TB3Q4BV8##Blog_1178497##q1_a1##30Z7M1Q8U0YZUW5TQYXUSQEG3YP8AD", "type": "mcq", "stem": "We left and went to Starkville as Alan is shopping for a Kawasaki Teryx ( ATV ) . Then we came home , then left again to go Columbus to pick up meds , shop at Belk 's , then ate supper at Doug and Hazel 's . Finally , we came home around 7 pm .\n\nQuestion: What kind of day has it been ?", "options": {"A": "It was n't that long of a day .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "It 's been a long day .", "D": "It 's been a short day ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 11850, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3K3IX1W4S6P56Z53SHN5MELYZTGAPK##3U5JL4WY5L7YZ3P7VATXS8HPMVY4XM##A37IJGXG1VEBEK##Blog_68239##q1_a1##362E9TQF2J4TTTU9LK1V11JX4J4GIQ", "type": "mcq", "stem": "The porkwalk connected the barns of Leering Turnip Junction to the Sneaky Punchfork Open Ocelot Vestibule , a cleverly - misnamed stapler museum made completely out of carp and featuring the world 's first gift shop to ever adopt the policy of treating every customer who spent thirty dollars or more to a brutal bludgeoning . We went there whenever it was our destination . It was Wednesday . We liked badminton .\n\nQuestion: What may happen after we went to the musuem ?", "options": {"A": "We played squash", "B": "We played batminton", "C": "We played tennis", "D": "We played racquetball"}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 18918, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3TZ0XG8CBUI6VOWHEU7U4XFO48W89V##3I7DHKZYGOYZV02M9L6LRTNWJP45FF##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_151919##q1_a1##3ZFRE2BDQBSQA5E9AYPLPIMI3SDZXL", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Work suffered in the process , but I sure did enjoy playing in the ocean and sitting on the beaches . That 's the problem when you work for yourself . It 's easy to get distracted , and harder to get back to work .\n\nQuestion: What may be a fact about this person ?", "options": {"A": "They struggle with work .", "B": "They are a boss at a company .", "C": "They are their own boss .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 6300, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3N5YJ55YXIHKX3SXW0MDAN4BSKOANL##3570Y55XZSYI6D78F4T0C99ALTYYG8##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_790643##q1_a1##3UAU495MIK6MUX673K3HPDGAP9WOUP", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Drawing the collar and leash as well as a bone and paw prints , representations of the dog without actually drawing it . Abstract expressionism is something else we touched on . Mark Rothko ( 1903 - 1970 ) was a member of the New York School group .\n\nQuestion: What subject is the narrator interested in ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "They like the New York Yankees .", "C": "They like media .", "D": "They like art ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 23087, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3R868ACW4SA0UUKC1QDH9YYF7IHZGD##3VBEN272MLX6F2WSW1PB2PX0WUNSGO##AB1VYJNM0H69F##Blog_424062##q2_a1##3TZ0XG8CBWYLPDVOYSJUWV3WX8N98Z", "type": "mcq", "stem": "A deafening explosion rang out . I was sure it was God telling me that we had gone too far . Our four companions rushed out of the house to assess the situation , convinced , I ' m sure , that the two of us were responsible for the explosion that had rendered the house without power .\n\nQuestion: How many campanions did the narrator have ?", "options": {"A": "Between 5 - 7 companions", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "Between 1 - 3 companions", "D": "Between 8 - 9 companions"}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 2279, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3ZQX1VYFTFJOW0ZU0H2CTLYMTQ7O8V##30X31N5D665K00IWUY91Y1A68MQASF##A31M81P0W93QF3##Blog_18844##q1_a1##3ZXNP4Z39TZCQ1REDKUEN4YXNA7L7H", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Not sure how I will feel on Saturday , which is a shame because I have some shipping to do and probably dinner with friends . And Friday I work until 9PM at the Festival , so that will be a further drain on my energy . Whee !\n\nQuestion: What may happen after friday ?", "options": {"A": "I will find some more work to do .", "B": "I will get overtime .", "C": "I will party all night .", "D": "I will be to exhausted to do something productive ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 1501, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3OZ4VAIBEXDTCC538Z9HL5DZBZSVJD##3TXWC2NHN0OR0S9KIVJ1A8BDTSX9S6##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_520526##q1_a1##3VIVIU06FMQTL3QVWNZQE63U03ZMIJ", "type": "mcq", "stem": "At the end of the session , I was so relaxed . I have to have 2 more sessions until she 'll start correcting the neck problem again . I would definately suggest acupuncture for anybody experiencing severe muscle pain .\n\nQuestion: What will happen if the neck pain does not immediately go away ?", "options": {"A": "The narrator will get more time with the chiropractor .", "B": "The narrator will get more acupuncture done .", "C": "The narrator will get more medicine .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 21668, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3B9J25CZ25BQC6IT4CNQNEGXMWNSCV##351SEKWQS1F05N9WAESHKVVXU8NDME##A1F0NR3E2VWUIO##Blog_232858##q1_a1##3KA7IJSNW8JPJY92ITZ19NTCAS6BPV", "type": "mcq", "stem": "We cleaned him up as well as we could . The cell in which we lived had a concrete slab in the middle on which we slept . Four naked light bulbs hung in each corner of the room .\n\nQuestion: What might have happened to him before we helped clean him up ?", "options": {"A": "He had been beaten up after being tossed in the cell .", "B": "He had been beaten up and then tossed in the cell .", "C": "He had lived and slept in a concrete slab .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 7467, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3URJ6VVYUPL8JADL4G0ZKBU8XPL4O5##33OOO72IVIJUDQT2JFYIM3873Z6CTF##A22EDUBB602EJD##Blog_208179##q1_a1##3ZXV7Q5FJD2W2QCEIQZR8DLQQ5RCF4", "type": "mcq", "stem": "It turned out to be a roasted pepper , stuffed with bland vegetables on a bed of noodles in sweet chilli sauce . Weird . I did n't eat much of it ... I made 2 chocolate pecan pies to have when we got back , but we never had it .\n\nQuestion: What did the person think the was strange about the situation ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "This person had never eaten a roasted pepper with vegetables inside it .", "C": "This person thought he was hungry but did not each much .", "D": "This person thought it was strange for food to be on the bed ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 9482, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3N7PQ0KLI73GJCGZUM4KXSWW78T3E6##3FE7TXL1LL2JIH8FPFRHXJC7ARR2QJ##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1513897##q1_a1##3FULMHZ7OWBZDWRGBYXMK5TBVQUM4A", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I ' m also going to have to work extra hard in Russian because there are only two levels and the more advanced one is slightly too advanced for me , but I do n't want to go to the beginners and be absolutely frustrated for months as they try to grasp the alphabet and the structure and rules of a slavic language , which for me comes naturally seeing as Polish and Russian are similar . French should be easy enough , so at least I 'll have some space to breathe there . I ' m not looking forward to getting up at 7 am everyday ! !\n\nQuestion: What type of language is the narrator trying to learn .", "options": {"A": "They are working hard on French .", "B": "They are working hard on Polish .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "They are working hard on Russian ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 2614, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3UY4PIS8QRJ99QGQGJHK7ON0VTJ1NJ##38F5OAUN5OAYW07BS49ISYD5RO97HK##A1F0NR3E2VWUIO##Blog_1270753##q1_a1##3WGZLY9VCJ0XS385A8OWIRMMO1LD8J", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Things are getting better . Though today we ' ve had alot of rain , I had loads of fun hanging out with Kristen . She and her friend Steve who is pretty cool were my company today . We went bowling . Not the duckpin kind the other .\n\nQuestion: Why might have we gone bowling ?", "options": {"A": "We went bowling because it would be loads of fun hanging out with Kristen .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "We went bowling because the rain encouraged us indoors .", "D": "We went bowling because the weather was getting better ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 7628, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3OCZWXS7ZO5I98EO5T3HXMWS2AHL54##30MVJZJNHNBY1PQUV1ANI7KQYF09JJ##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_704782##q1_a1##3DWNFENNE599COLV81KU4D1URYFJ4N", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Finally , more than a month after taking the lens back to the shop , I have it back in my hands . It works . The zoom 's smooth . And I ' m feeling - not for the first time - as though I ' ve been hung out to dry .\n\nQuestion: What may be the reason they feel hung out to dry ?", "options": {"A": "Things are starting to look up .", "B": "They are making more money than they are spending .", "C": "They were wet when this started .", "D": "Things are not starting to go awry ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 3309, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "306W7JMRYYWPJHBECELQV3AES5NB8Q##3L2IS5HSFBGS475I8AX67AOLKDFNUE##A3JPYCC2U4D9CZ##Blog_430396##q1_a1##3D42WVSDHA995TDJEIHG54D9TRJYF4", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Saturday we went shopping for shirts for our family Christmas picture , and then we took our sisters ( Erin , Nicole & Marissa ) to see Enchanted . Super cute movie ! Then we went to my mom 's for dinner and took pictures . Family drama ( what else is new ) .\n\nQuestion: Where did the sisters go to see Enchanted ?", "options": {"A": "They went to the movie theater .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "They went to a shop .", "D": "They went to a mall ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 12455, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3W31J70BAUA7IC4SJ1QOOQDVYS4KCS##3DPNQGW4LOU0BD4IEKW7KTSEWFG46D##ALI92G1065WRG##Blog_685342##q1_a1##3R16PJFTS554N8RDQMK65S176RY4KY", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Unlike outside and backstage , it was cool in the bus . He mentally thanked their bus driver for switching on the airco this morning as he made his way to the living room area . He flopped down on the large , brown sofa and closed his eyes , sighing again .\n\nQuestion: Why would the air in the bus be turned on ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "To help with mental switching their train of thought .", "C": "To block out external noise when they close their eyes to sleep .", "D": "To raise the temperature and combat the cool air ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 9108, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3XU80RHWHZE4FH33LWLQ6DO3FNJ446##3WQ3B2KGE9EAU1PN3WID5DJUOMS1BE##APRZ7BR8C0ZMQ##Blog_901409##q1_a2##3SBX2M1TKDLB4MQ1JTS39GP8CVZ4QJ", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I did n't even managed to say ' bye ' or anything when we got back 'cause I got to our bathroom in a record time lol I guess you can imagine the rest of the story . That was a few hours ago . A while ago I thought I 'd read the info for the antibiotics I have for the bacterial skin infection . Really , it did n't surprise me that there was ' common side effects : blah blah blah , NAUSEA , blah blah blah ' .\n\nQuestion: What is the reason I got to the bathroom so quickly ?", "options": {"A": "I vomited and had to hurry .", "B": "I had a simple need to go", "C": "I wanted to brush my teeth .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 14857, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3S829FDFT4FN749DIG0OYQ3GGL8DXU##340UGXU9D1GK71DYUYVX9P67ESMUVO##A1WAWEY2810TFN##Blog_1243708##q1_a1##32W3UF2EZQZM4AFPY938H9O02Z44C1", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Anger is a seed . It plants itself in you starting off as a dull ache and then begins to burn in your center like a fist of fire until it begins to grow and creep its way through your body stretching it 's fingers up your spine and tickling your brain and then down again to your toes , rooting you to the ground . The anger I feel ... I did n't notice it at first or if I did it was minor and I could push it aside . But now it breathes in me like some kind of beast that continues to remind me of it 's presence and whisper its fruitful - sour thoughts and intentions in my ear .\n\nQuestion: What should this person do ?", "options": {"A": "Shout at their co - workers", "B": "Take anger management classes", "C": "Should at their family", "D": "Go and beat someone up"}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 20830, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3VZYA8PITOW5CCP2G0HYZ244YLM057##3OJSZ2ATDTUMG7NGR28931AFH6Y57U##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_404778##q1_a1##34R3P23QHSZA0VAIA9BSVUGY527WH8", "type": "mcq", "stem": "In one village , the first person who dared to shake my hand was an elderly woman with a heavily lined face . She looked into my eyes and had a huge warm smile . I asked my Somali colleagues why the kids do n't want to shake my hand . I have to say I was n't prepared for the reply .\n\nQuestion: Why may the narrator not feel welcome in the village ?", "options": {"A": "The narrator is a racist .", "B": "The narrator feels in danger .", "C": "Younger people are wary of him .", "D": "The narrator feels unsafe ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 11954, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3IKDQS3DQEY1ISFXZ0TCJCAACI0CI5##37U1UTWH9WKFL8QXYEDIK2B6JZZR84##APRZ7BR8C0ZMQ##Blog_1475689##q1_a2##382GHPVPHSPJXLKZLIG7W8WX23K34E", "type": "mcq", "stem": "He 's been waking up later and later these days , as if it 's getting more and more difficult , and that concerns me . I think the insomnia he 's been suffering is really starting to catch up with him . He has low blood pressure to begin with , and these issues with his sleep cycle are no help . \" \" Sanzo , low blood pressure ? \"\n\nQuestion: If he gets up later and later then how can he have insomnia ?", "options": {"A": "Insomnia is a food addiction .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "Insomnia means you are unable to have relations .", "D": "Insomnia is the fact of oversleeping ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 5329, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3C8QQOM6JRF9FL8AWBYBETO508LIL9##36AHBNMV1URFUTXHDESS6O6D9INDYH##A39SK1E6IMQBD5##Blog_798659##q1_a1##3VMV5CHJZATJ27AKFW0ZF8L6FC3GTE", "type": "mcq", "stem": "They offer with attractive high commission rates in the entire industry . Rx Commission is the best Rx affiliate program on the web , they also have the best Rx affiliate resources on affiliate marketing in general . At Rx Affiliates Resources , ther are informative articles and pointers on how to get started making money with affiliate programs and implementing an affiliate strategy on your site . There are some payment system you may choose that accepted on your resource system like Epassporte Rx affiliate payment is ok . There are fees , but depending on how much money you are receiving , its not too bad .\n\nQuestion: What may be a plausible fact about me ?", "options": {"A": "I want people to avoid the affiliate program .", "B": "I want people to try out the affiliate program .", "C": "I want people to leave the affiliate program .", "D": "I want people to sell the affiliate program ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 12130, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3E9VAUV7BWCZFDX4J4JOZ5EA2C2AYO##36V4Q8R5ZLYUUWD1F0Y1KU2W8JXMQ0##APRZ7BR8C0ZMQ##Blog_394932##q1_a1##3YGYP136417X2VF7EDWZDF5DZZ2NR6", "type": "mcq", "stem": "In reality , it was sand . Sand used to make the finest glass . After the war , the Barcid king had ordered that no glass was to be given to outsiders at any cost . Thus , over the years , glass had become scarce and the process of glass making lost to the world .\n\nQuestion: What is the reason the Barcid King ordered no glass was to be given to outsiders ?", "options": {"A": "He wanted the glass making trade to be rarer and his kingdom would be known for it .", "B": "He wanted to punish his subjects and make them go glassless .", "C": "He did n't want anyone to wear glasses .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 11641, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "31ANT7FQNAGVH1U5Y60JXSRTDKBH5P##3QRYMNZ7F1WSZJP0S2JWUCQS4UJNTC##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_332541##q1_a1##3M47JKRKCZFY7UTQ0LGICLCU7CB68R", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I feel so sad sometimes that i ' m not involved in theatre anymore , and when i think about it 's like i have all this energy building up and i need to just go and do a musical . Anyways , i just transferred to a new college , and i met a friend . She is really crazy and very outgoing ! but she is such a great friend !\n\nQuestion: What may be a fact about this person 's past ?", "options": {"A": "They used to do theatre acting .", "B": "They transferred out of their theatre program .", "C": "They did n't have time anymore to do theatre .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 6865, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3P7RGTLO6EB4V88NFPIXQXZZ5JAKAT##3Z7ISHFUH1TONZCO8V7V65D5WEXZ8K##AUTYWXILTACCR##Blog_1136619##q1_a2##35XW21VSVISY9ZB61NSPIVUS9YSLST", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Currently he is standing in line at the ice cream store , Berry and Jen 's . The line is wrapped around the partisan and about to overflow into the street . The open door carries in with it the sounds of the busy tourist town .\n\nQuestion: What is the reason that the line for the ice cream store is so incredibly long that it stretches straight out the door ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "Demand for this ice cream is exceptionally high , because it is expertly crafted and the price is right", "C": "They are the only ice cream store in town to accept food stamps and for this reason have a high volume of customers day in and day out", "D": "They are having a buy one get two free special that is simply too tantalizing for the locals to think of passing up"}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 21960, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3PA41K45VPI2HM6C5CNL4L7GR2C7P2##3TPZPLC3M3RN3N3JT2QXGORPEXQP3Q##AABCSDU3TZLNG##Blog_18564##q1_a1##3EN4YVUOUE60AQ95SCMZ1OYSK08JX4", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Then I went to Rite Aid to pick up Sue 's prescriptions . After that , I went to Torchy 's and got a sandwich for dinner since I was starving and running out of time . At home , I opened up the house to cool things down and fed the cats . I changed into cooler clothes and ate my sandwich while watching the beginning of the Mariners game .\n\nQuestion: What was the weather like today ?", "options": {"A": "It was a hot and summery day .", "B": "It was cold and dreary .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "It was pouring rain ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 8748, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3XEIP58NL21VABXKWFMXEORVWJPLZ7##3E337GFOLCNOUE3U82KPVTB3IB1NGJ##A3R19ZA45J8915##Blog_1022473##q1_a1##3KL228NDMX0KZOKXLNM7EHYAWYTKGR", "type": "mcq", "stem": "So I lost my job at the massage clinic . They needed to downsize and the other receptionist was the owner 's daughter , so I got the boot . What makes me feel raw about it is they did n't give me any notice .\n\nQuestion: What caused me to lose my job at the massage clinic ?", "options": {"A": "They had n't told me I needed to be licensed .", "B": "The owner 's daughter did not like me too much .", "C": "They said I was terrible at giving massages .", "D": "They needed to reduce the amount of workers ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 22997, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "39WICJI5AV6EU77VQ9IXI2XEW433ZU##3X31TUMD70112ZA6E6J7BE38CLVL1H##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_652611##q1_a2##3I6NF2WGIIAHH5ZUE0I1CSFT0NM5GC", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Another car pulled up and that body was also whisked away . By this time there were about five police officers on motorcycles at the scene . One officer was vainly trying to sop up the largest pool of blood with a rag or towel . The whole episode took about two minutes . No sooner had the second body been taken away than people were again walking along the footpath , literally stepping over blood , seemingly taking no notice or perhaps too afraid to stop . No crowd of onlookers gathered and no crime scene was set up . There was no collection of evidence and any forensic evidence was being contaminated .\n\nQuestion: Why would there be police at the scene ?", "options": {"A": "There was a death .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "There was an attack on the crowd via terrorism .", "D": "There was a murder ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 22398, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3QMELQS6Y59PVA9FFWAIB4JR3S8R6W##31QTRG6Q2UB9O110YQ7NEKZTCE7PYI##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_773960##q1_a2##3FO95NVK5CYUI87CM9DLC9FJMX2SRD", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I find life hard enough . But here I am , doing a spring \" cleanse . \" I am cranky because I am exhausted . I am exhausted - or feeling my exhaustion - because all I ' ve been drinking is green tea , and not my usual 2 large cups of coffee in the morning plus limitless cups of black tea throughout the afternoon , and then decaf black tea in the evening .\n\nQuestion: What will happen to the narrator after taking all these liquids ?", "options": {"A": "The narrator will need to get more water .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "The narrator will need to use the restroom .", "D": "The narrator will be fully hydrated ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 21234, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "31MCUE39BKKZ91DJGJI85XT0SUNG3G##3J2UYBXQQMA4H0NABMX5GSES9Q760P##A1VR49TB3Q4BV8##Blog_1562479##q1_a1##3INZSNUD824X68RFF0UAINHX823D9Y", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I think this was the \" something \" I needed to hit me hard enough . [ /sarcasm ] Hey , one stubborn girl , nearly two months later plus really painful doctor visits and rehabilitation and what does that get you ? MORE SURGERY !\n\nQuestion: How do I feel about the surgery ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "I want to experience it again and again .", "C": "I love it and it 's perfect .", "D": "It 's a great experience ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 2339, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3VIVIU06FMQTL3QVWNZQE63U0IHIMR##34Q075JO10SO53LKPDXODUBK9N1105##A2WPPQC8S3ICVZ##Blog_1154534##q2_a1##3LXX8KJXPYNOA5I4598QTHTXD5WO99", "type": "mcq", "stem": "DENVER We d . August 27th - There were some tense moments at the Unconventional Denver convergence space Wednesday morning when police set up a perimeter around it and attempted to enter and search the building . Security at the space demanded a search warrant when police asked to enter the space . Legal aid was called to the scene immediately where video and written accounts were taken . Police were unable to obtain a warrant and left after some time , but not before arresting 2 activists outside the center .\n\nQuestion: What may be the reason the police left ?", "options": {"A": "They interviewed officials .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "They could n't find anything .", "D": "They did n't have a warrant ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 19960, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3Q2T3FD0OPMEV08CBKS3A015HYHM3O##3SUWZRL0M1SI3F1B3Q8KTF45BSN6EC##AW1QY7Q83DYCJ##Blog_285862##q2_a1##31YWE12TE2Q7QV83R3X2YYTKUJ0X7Y", "type": "mcq", "stem": "It took me a long time to wake up this morning , so he was watching me sleep / wake up . He snuggled up close and my heart just melted . Playing with his curls I just could n't believe how real and how perfect this is . I love him so much .\n\nQuestion: Whose curls was she play with ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "She was cuddling and curling up with her pillow .", "C": "She was playing with her young son 's curls .", "D": "She was snuggling and playing with the curls of her teddy bear ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 20806, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "338431Z1FLDFKGFJFSWCS45IPZ5OR0##3TESA3PJ32839HF9N7RK3LIR2LRMME##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_919105##q1_a2##3BDORL6HKMRT5GHN9LZLP2Z9TT6RCI", "type": "mcq", "stem": "At like 3:30 Foot got on again and I was talked into going into his chat and that 's where serious lolz ensued . We talked about the party and he is def coming and he 's actually stoked for it . I do n't know how I feel about this .\n\nQuestion: What will happen at the upcoming party ?", "options": {"A": "Foot will be a maybe for attendance .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "Foot will be there .", "D": "Foot will not show up ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 5607, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3BJKPTD2QCAVX8KRB9IBMEB5OV7RTM##3W8CV64QJ3X2AJV471726U4BKH39H8##AB1VYJNM0H69F##Blog_701585##q2_a1##35JDMRECC6NHDOSNP1B4GML5COHEGV", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I had a dentist appointment earlier this week . Anyone who knows me knows that there are few things I hate more than going to the dentist . Growing up , I went to a great dentist , and in general , my teeth are in pretty good shape , but I ' ve had a few fillings done , and I ca n't imagine that anyone enjoys that . When I moved to D.C. and signed up for insurance , I opted to not add on the additional dental insurance , but when I got my new insurance info for 2008 , it appeared that my insurance company had opted to add on some dental benefits .\n\nQuestion: What is true of the narrator 's insurance ?", "options": {"A": "Growing up , their family had dental insurance .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "They need to have dental insurance .", "D": "They company went against their wishes ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 17502, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3R6RZGK0XHQY1QZ9EXMKNQGVHSOVYK##345LHZDED070VSBFAOPRQUEONSTU3V##A2RUHO7I7Y4XFA##Blog_222608##q1_a1##3LCXHSGDLVKK3T1EK15L50491R3ESU", "type": "mcq", "stem": "During the hearing , he sat quietly at counsel table looking down . When it was time for him to make his remarks to the court , it was hard for him to talk and when he did speak , it was very hard for everyone to hear him , even with the microphone . I think the enormity of his crimes has finally started to sink in . In his remarks to the court , he said , \" I do n't want to be a monster , \" and \" I ca n't even conceive the amount of pain that I have caused .\n\nQuestion: Was the crime severe ?", "options": {"A": "The crimes were overrated", "B": "The crimes caused little pain", "C": "The crimes were enormous", "D": "The crimes were petty"}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 23892, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "337F8MIIM1R2AIK9MTAOM8MYRSF048##3T3IWE1XG92D2G2S8UBDY6LXB1VQTL##AGTKQI9PCODC5##Blog_695320##q1_a1##34KYK9TV2TMMWQPUAA3V4SYNXA9BS3", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Also , that intro to Medieval Studies class that I could n't find online but need for the Medieval Studies Certificate is being offered this year spring semester instead of fall semester , because the canadian professor ran into some immigration issues . Whups . But that works out cause I 'll still get to take it my first year , but I do n't have to take ALL intro classes my first semester . Instead I ' m taking Intro to Latin Paleography , which I am SO excited about .\n\nQuestion: In what semester am I at the university ?", "options": {"A": "I am in my second semester in spring .", "B": "I am in my fifth semester because I had some issues with Intro to Latin Paleography .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "I am beginning my first semester in fall ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 8021, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3UOMW19E6D4P64KISGAIU3658X15CY##3TU5ZICBREZF97BXLZOIFC11RJZ8Q2##A3H0TLQC53H5MB##Blog_1349166##q2_a1##31SIZS5W5BTXZHR6E30G97OQX3UQRZ", "type": "mcq", "stem": "So ya ... this last week has been a little off i feel like , and he wo nt talk to me abt it . I think he may just be stressed with school and work , but i ' m really scared that its me ... that he is starting to not like me , not love me anymore . idk how that would even be possible , i mean things are going great . but idk .. i ' m scared i love him too much , i ' m scared i love him more then he loves me .... idk .\n\nQuestion: What best describe 's the OP 's personality ?", "options": {"A": "Insecure", "B": "Independent", "C": "Absent", "D": "Confident"}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 5354, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "37NXA7GVST4Z72T3BKLU1KQRF9VVLJ##34T446B1C1CTXHWBLDA82S6266A0CS##A2X2CN7XX6C96N##Blog_1304592##q1_a2##3CVDZS288JE9BCO5VFT5B9Q2KLMFMK", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I always felt bad for looking up to him . He would constantly say , \" Be your own man . You do n't need someone else to lift you up to where THEY are . Lift yourself up to where YOU need to be . \" I do n't feel bad for looking up to him anymore .\n\nQuestion: Why do n't I feel bad for looking up to him anymore ?", "options": {"A": "He gave me bad advice .", "B": "He gave me hope .", "C": "He gave me useless tips .", "D": "He gave me money ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 15147, "label_index": 1}}
